Paulo Mariano



github.com/paulomarian0 🚺



paulomariano2501@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/paulomarian0

I am a Full Stack Developer with a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and a postgraduate degree in Software Engineering. I have skills in JavaScript, Node.js, React, Vue, and .NET, as well as knowledge in AWS infrastructure. I have experience in creating comprehensive and efficient solutions from backend to frontend.

Professional Experience

Front-End Developer

LocX Gestão de Imóveis Comerciais - Since 04/2024

- Developed and implemented improvements in the front-end development of the company's internal projects, assisted in refactoring and creating new screens, enhancing project performance.
- Collaborated in teams on relevant and impactful projects, improving my leadership skills, effective communication, problem-solving ability, and critical thinking in a dynamic and challenging environment.

Full Stack Developer

ILUMEO - 03/2023 to 04/2024

- Worked on the development of existing projects and the creation of new internal projects for the company, and was one of the key contributors to a project that served approximately 500,000 users.
- Worked on the development of Web and Mobile (PWA) projects using React, Node, Express, Vue, Prisma, TypeScript, and AWS.

Full Stack Developer

Ketra Soluções Inteligentes - 08/2022 to 01/2023

- Worked alongside another developer on a project for a company, where I was responsible for all the front-end development using TypeScript and React.
- Occasionally worked on the backend development built in .NET, implementing new routes, functionalities, and applying Clean Code principles and Domain Driven Design (DDD) architecture.

Full Stack Developer

Infosis Consultoria e Sistemas - 06/2021 to 08/2022

- I was one of the people responsible for creating new features and maintaining the existing code of the Espírito Santo Development Bank (BANDES) system, working with .NET and ExtJS.
- I worked on an international project where I was responsible for the project along with two interns, using .NET and ReactJS.

Technical Skills

.NET • JavaScript • Typescript • NodeJS • ReactJS • VueJS • NodeJs • Git • AWS • CI/CD

Education

Computer Science

Universidade Vila Velha (UVV) - 02/2019 to 11/2022

Postgraduate in Software Engineering

Descomplica Faculdade Digital - 06/2023 to 01/2024